Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 49, folder: 35 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 25: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 26: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    November 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 28: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 29: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    Auguat 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    August 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 32: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    Spring 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 34: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 35: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Item 36: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    May 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    November 9172. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    November 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    February 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Personnel Management Association Inc. Association Newsletter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 35)
    May 1973. Item is in English.
- Box: 49, folder: 36 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: About The Personnel Psychology Center of New York: Sales Aptitude Testoing Corporation, Publication (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Box: 49, folder: 37 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of the P.C.K. Employees' Union, Independent, Publication (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws of the P.C.K. Employees' Union, Independent, Publication (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Peter Cailler Kohler Swiss Chocolates Company Inc., of Fulton, New York and Peter Cailler Kohler Employees' Union Independent, Publication (Box 49, Folder 37)
    July 10, 1951. Item is in English.
- Box: 49, folder: 38 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Pfaudler Permutit Reporter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: Facts for Employee Applicants, Publication (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: Pfaudler Permutit Inc.: Employee Annual Report, Publication (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Box: 49, folder: 39 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Pfizer to Fight Antitrust Jury Verdict, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Pfizer Annual Report, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: PfizerInterim Report to Share Owners, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: The Pfizer Scene, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
    January 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Report of 1964 Annual Meeting of Share Owners, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 6: Annual Report for the Year 1963 Chas. Pfizer & Co., Inc., Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 7: Report of 1965 Annual Meeting of Share Holders, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 8: Pfizer Interim Report to Share Owners, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 9: Pfizer Interim Report to Share Owners, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 10: The World of Discovery: Pfizer Annual Report 1967, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 11: Chas. Pfizer & Co., Inc. Annual Report 1951, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 12: The Pilsbury Company: Annual Report for theYear Ended May 31, 1960, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 13: Information About the Corporation, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
    October 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Business Week: Search for a Universal Name, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
    June 4, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Pfaudler Permutit Reporter, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
    Vol. XX. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Application for Technical Employment, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 17: Annual Report for 1961 Chas. Pfizer & Co., Inc., Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 18: Report of 1961 Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 19: Report of 1963 Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 20: Pfizer Annual Report 1952, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 21: Annual Report for the Year 1964 Chas. Pfizer & Co., Inc., Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Item 22: Pfizer Pulse, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
    February 21, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Pfizer Scene, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
    January-February 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Box: 49, folder: 40 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Pfizer Scene, Publication (Box 49, Folder 40)
    October 1976. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 1 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Chas. Pfizer & Co., Inc Employment Record Report, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Chas. Pfizer anc Co., Inc. Application for Employment, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Your Career Opportunities in Hospitals, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: You and Pfizer, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your Career Opportunities in Pharmacy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Your Career Opportunities in Medicine, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Key Man in a key spot in the '60s, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Previous Employment Letter, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Chemical Engineering is the name of the game, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Eight Cylinder Marketing Man, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Box: 50, folder: 2 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Then - 1849 and Now - 1961: More than a Century and a Decade of Progress, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Background Informationa dn Comment on the Recent Antibiotics Antitrust Suit, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Our Smallest Servants, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: men, molds and molecules, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Box: 50, folder: 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Philadelphia Gas Works Division of The United Gas Improvement Company: Procedure, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employee Opinion Survey at Philadelphia Gas Works, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: P.G.W. News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    May 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: P.G.W. News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    July-August 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter to employees, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    May 17, 1956. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 4 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Application for Interview, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Welcome, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Welcome, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Fuel for Thought, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Box: 50, folder: 5 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Letter to New Employee, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Agreement betweeen Philadelphia Gas Works Division of The United Gas Improvement Company and the Gas Works Employees' Union, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Agreement betweeen Philadelphia Gas Works Division of The United Gas Improvement Company and the Gas Works Employees' Union, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Grievance Report, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Agreement betweeen Philadelphia Gas Works Company and the Gas Works Employees' Union, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Box: 50, folder: 6 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A Minute Please!, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    May 8, 1962. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 7 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Co-Operative Plan, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The Mitten Plan for Collective Consideration and Co-Operative Benefits, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Box: 50, folder: 8 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Personnel Statistics, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
    November 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Master Board Gives Company Control of Grievances, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Functional Organization Chart, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The Philadelphia Transportation Company, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Box: 50, folder: 9 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Historical Sketch, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Your Future with the Company Moving Into Tomorrow, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Box: 50, folder: 10 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Philco News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Vol. 1 No. 1. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 11 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol. 10 No. 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol. 10 special report. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol. 10 No. 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol. 10 No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol. 10 No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol. 9 no> 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 8 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol No 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 6 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 5 No 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 7 No 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Vol 9 No 4. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 12 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Relocation Policy and Procedure, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Johnny PresentsThe House That You Built, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Box: 50, folder: 13 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: about Philip Morris, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: This is Philip Morris, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: This is Philip Morris, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Johnny PresentsThe House That You Built, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: A E Lyon, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: This is Philip Morris, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Thje Philip Morris Story, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Box: 50, folder: 14 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    December 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    January 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    November 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    October 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 18 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 18 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 18 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 18 No 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 19 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: General Factory Rules for Employes of Philip Morris U.S.A., Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    June 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: News Correction, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 19 No1. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 19 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 19 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 19 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Call News Special Edition, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    August 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Vol 18 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    February 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    March 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Call News Kentucky Derby, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 21: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    May 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    July 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    June 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    August 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Call News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    October 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 15 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 12 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 12 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 12 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 12 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 12 No0 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Philip Morris News Special, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 12 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 11 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 11 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    April 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 11 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 11 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 11 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 24: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 13 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 14 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Focus: for and about Philip Morris people, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 3 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 16 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 16 No 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 16 No 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 15 No 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 16 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 16 No 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 18 No 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 17 No 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Philip Morris News, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Vol 18 No 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 50, folder: 16 (Box 50, Folder 16)